<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<world>
	<location id="1" name="Alabastia">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="1">
				You are standing in Alabastia, your hometown. You see your mothers house, but know nobody is home right now.
				Beside it is Prof. Oaks laboratory. You should hurry so you wont be late for your appointment with Prof. Oak.
				To the north you see the beginning of Route 1.
			</InformationEvent>
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="201">
				You are standing in Alabastia, your hometown. You see your mothers house, but know nobody is home right now.
				Beside it is Prof. Oaks laboratory. To the north you see the beginning of Route 1.
			</InformationEvent>
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="402">
				You are standing in Alabastia, your hometown. You see your mothers house, but know nobody is home right now.
				Beside it is Prof. Oaks laboratory. Why don't you go in and tell Oak the passphrase he's looking for?
			</InformationEvent>
			<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="enter laboratory" nextLocId="2" reqToken="">
				You move towards Prof. Oaks laboratory and open the heavy doors.
			</ChangeLocationEvent>
			<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go north" nextLocId="3" reqToken="">
				You go north to Route 1.
			</ChangeLocationEvent>
	</location>
	<location id="2" name="Prof. Oaks laboratory">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="2">
				You are in Prof. Oaks huge laboratory. All around you are his weird science machines, you probably shouldn't
				touch them. At the end of the room you see a frustrated Prof. Oak.
			</InformationEvent>
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="201">
				You are in Prof. Oaks huge laboratory. All around you are his weird science machines, you probably shouldn't
				touch them. At the end of the room you see a frustrated Prof. Oak waiting for your return.
			</InformationEvent>
			<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="talk to oak" reqToken="2">
				<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
					As you approach Prof. Oak he starts talking: "Good that you're finally here! I need your help.
					A good friend of mine named John did some work on my computer, but now I can't remember the password 
					he set for me. I can't leave my lab right now, so could you please go to John and tell him I sent you? 
					He'll tell you my password then.
					Great thank you, but hurry!"
					After this Prof. Oak turns his back on you and starts yelling at one of his assistants.
				</InformationEvent>
				<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="1"/>
				<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="2"/>
				<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="201"/>
			</CompoundEvent>
			<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="talk to oak" reqToken="402">
				<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
					"Finally, you made it back! So what's the password? Oh really? PIKACHU again? I guess I should have
					tried that... Whatever, thanks so much for your help! Here have a Pikachu of your own and go on an adventure!"
				</InformationEvent>
				<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="402"/>
			</CompoundEvent>
			<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="leave laboratory" reqToken="" nextLocId="1">
				You exit Prof. Oaks laboratory and return to the streets of Alabastia.
			</ChangeLocationEvent>
	</location>
	<location id="3" name="Route 1">
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="3">
			You are walking down Route 1, just north of Alabastia. Up ahead you see a woman walking her Fukano. 
			The road continues to the east, to the west you see a large forest.
		</InformationEvent>
		<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go south" reqToken="" nextLocId="1">
			You go south down Route 1 and return to Alabastia. Maybe your mom's back home?
		</ChangeLocationEvent>
		<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go east" reqToken="" nextLocId="4">
			You go east towards John's house.
		</ChangeLocationEvent>
		<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go west" reqToken="" nextLocId="5">
			You go west towards the forest.
		</ChangeLocationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="talk to woman" reqToken="3">
			You talk to the woman as her Fukano regards you with an interested gaze.
			" Oh hi, how are you doing? You're looking for John? He just came by here and went east towards
			his house. I hope I could help."
			As you leave she smiles at you and her Fukano barks twice, releasing little flames into the air.
		</InformationEvent>
		
	</location>
	<location id="4" name="Infront of John's house">
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="4">
			You're standing in front of a large wooden house. Standing at the door is a man you presume is John. He doesn't look happy.
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="401">
			You're standing in front of John's house. John is sitting beside the door waiting for you to bring his key.
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="402">
			You're standing in front of John's house.
		</InformationEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="talk to john" reqToken="4">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				The man approaches you and says: "Hi my name's John. What? You need my help? Well I'll need yours first.
				You see, I just lost my keys in the forest to the west of Route 1, and can't get into my house. I'd get
				them myself, but I think I saw a bear there, so I'm too scared. But you should be fine eh? Get me my keys
				and I'll help you with whatever you need."
				After your conversation John sits down beside his door.
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="4"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="401"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="talk to john" reqToken="401">
			"Hey, you got my keys yet?"
		</InformationEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="give keys to john" reqToken="401;501">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				You give John his keys.
				"Hey you got them! Awesome! Okay, with what do you need help? Oh Oak forgot his password again?
				Man he's really getting old eh? Okay, the password is PIKACHU. Thanks again friend!"
				With these words John opens his door.
				"Oh, it wasn't even locked... Oh well."
				After these words he vanishes in his house. Time to get back and give Prof. Oak his password.
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="401"/>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="501"/>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="503"/>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="504"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="402"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go west" reqToken="" nextLocId="3">
			You go back west to Route 1.
		</ChangeLocationEvent>
	</location>
	<location id="5" name="Forest to the west of Route 1">
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="5">
			You arrive at the edge of the forest. It's pretty dark, you probably shouldn't go in any further.
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="5;401">
			You arrive at the edge of the forest. You see a large pile of leaves in front of you, and something that
			looks like a rabbit hole behind a tree. You also see some bear tracks. Maybe you should hurry with finding the keys.
			Rout 1 is to your east.
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="402">
			You arrive at the edge of the forest, but are too afraid of bears to go in any further...
		</InformationEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="examine rabbit hole" reqToken="5;401">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				You grope around in the rabbit hole, but find nothing. At the same time you start to hear growling noises.
				That bear seems to have heard you, you don't have much time left!
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="5"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="502"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="examine pile of leaves" reqToken="5;401">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				You shuffle through the leaves and hear metal clinging sounds. You found the key! At the same time you start
				to hear growling noises. That bear seems to have heard you, time to get back to John!
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="5"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="501"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="503"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="examine pile of leaves" reqToken="502">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				You shuffle through the leaves as fast as you can, and almost missed the metal object inside. You've got the
				keys, now run or that bear'll get you!!
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="502"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="501"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="504"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<CompoundEvent typ="2" command="examine rabbit hole" reqToken="503">
			<InformationEvent typ="0" command="" reqToken="">
				What the hell are you doing? You've got the keys and that bear is getting closer... Get out!
			</InformationEvent>
			<RemoveTokenEvent typ="3" command="" reqToken="" token="503"/>
			<GrantTokenEvent typ="4" command="" reqToken="" token="504"/>
		</CompoundEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="502">
			You're in the forest beside a rabbit hole. You see a pile of leaves and see a bear coming towards you...
			Route 1 is to your east.
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="503">
			You're in the forest beside pile of leaves. You see a rabbit hole behind a tree and a bear coming toward you...
			Route 1 is to your east
		</InformationEvent>
		<InformationEvent typ="0" command="look around" reqToken="504">
			The only thing you're aware of is the gigantic bear running towards you!
		</InformationEvent>
		<ChangeLocationEvent typ="1" command="go east" reqToken="" nextLocId="3">
			You turn around and run back to Route 1.
		</ChangeLocationEvent>
	</location>
</world>








